<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sci on Yujie Fu</title>
    <link>http://fyjhomepage.github.io/tags/sci/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sci on Yujie Fu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zn-Hans</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 14:40:04 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://fyjhomepage.github.io/tags/sci/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Effective Reversible Data Hiding in Encrypted Image with Adaptive Encoding Strategy</title>
      <link>http://fyjhomepage.github.io/%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E7%AF%87paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 14:40:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fyjhomepage.github.io/%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E7%AF%87paper/</guid>
      <description>#down{ width:20px; height:20px; } #topic{ color:#33ccff; word-spacing:nowrap; } #topic #T{ color:black; } Effective Reversible Data Hiding in Encrypted Image with Adaptive Encoding Strategy. Fu, Y., Kong, P., Yao, H., Tang, Z., &amp;amp; Qin, C. Information Sciences (2019). Abstract: Recently, reversible data hiding in encrypted image have attracted extensive attentions, which can be applied in secure cloud computing and privacy-preserving image processing. In this paper, a reversible data hiding scheme in encrypted image based on the adaptive encoding strategy is proposed. On the content-owner side, block permutation and stream cipher encryption are applied to mask the contents of original image. Through analyzing the distribution of MSB layers, embeddable blocks are first determined and auxiliary data are then generated by data hider. In order to vacate room for data accommodation, MSB layers of embeddable blocks are adaptively compressed according to occurrence frequency of MSB. Thus, additional data can be embedded into MSB layers of encrypted image together with reversed Huffman codewords and auxiliary data. Based on the availability of encryption key and data-hiding key, the receiver can realize separable operations of data extraction, image decryption and image recovery efficiently. Experimental results demonstrate that, our scheme not only can achieve satisfactory rate-distortion performance,</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>